resumebaking.com 2016-12-06

# Privacy Policy • ResumeBaking

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which ResumeBaking collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.resumebaking.com website (“Site”).  
This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by ResumeBaking.

### Personal identification information

We may collect personally identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, fill out a forms, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, contact information (name, email, address, phone number) and resume information (education, work history, personal skills, interests).  
We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us.  
Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site.  
Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.  
We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors.  
These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

### How we use collected information

ResumeBaking collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

To personalize user experience
    We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve customer service
    Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
To send periodic emails

The email address Users provide will only be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.  
If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others.  
We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

### Changes to this privacy policy

ResumeBaking has the discretion to update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at [contacts@resumebaking.com](mailto:contacts@resumebaking.com)

**This document was last updated on December 01, 2010**
